<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>visualización on Dominic Royé</title>
    <link>/es/tags/visualizaci%C3%B3n/</link>
    <description>Recent content in visualización on Dominic Royé</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2019 Dominic Royé. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/es/tags/visualizaci%C3%B3n/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clima y tiempo</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/climate/</guid>
      <description>Probability of a frost day (minimum temperature less than 0ºC) through the year in Europe. Data: E-OBS 18e.
   Probability of a frost day (minimum temperature less than 0ºC/32ºF) through the year in the Contiguous United States. Data: PRISM. Platform: Google Earth Engine.
Las anomalías invernales de temperatura y precipitación en Bilbao. Datos: ECA&amp;amp;D.Las anomalías invernales de temperatura y precipitación en Zaragoza.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geografía</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/geography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/geography/</guid>
      <description>Inspirado por el gran trabajo de @geo_coe, he creado un mapa de elevación para el río serpenteante Ebro, tramo medio entre Logroño y Zaragoza en España. Datos: Modelo Digital del Terreno - MDT05.Inspirado por el gran trabajo de @geo_coe, he creado un mapa de elevación para el río serpenteante Alagón, afluente más largo del río Tajo en España. Datos: Modelo Digital del Terreno - MDT05.Urban growth of Santiag de Compostela from before 1800 until today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medio ambiente</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/environment/</guid>
      <description>Light pollution by municipality in 2015. What is the municipality that emits the most artificial light? The map shows the Coefficient of Variation (standard deviation/mean) of each municipalities. Data: VIIRS Nighttime Lights NOAA (2015).Which coast has more light pollution in Peninsular Spain? The coast margins include a buffer of 5km. Data: VIIRS Nighttime Lights NOAA (2016).Light pollution by municipality in 2015. What is the municipality that emits the most artificial light?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Populación</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/population/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/population/</guid>
      <description>Population pyramid of Galicia since 1975. Data: IGEPopulation pyramid of Galician provinces since 1975. Data: IGEPopulation pyramid of Spanish autonomous community since 1998. Data: INEMigration flows between Spanish autonomous communities in 2008. Data: INE </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salud</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/health/</guid>
      <description>Evolution of adult obesity in Europe between 1975 and 2016. Data: ourwoldindata, script.National Overdose Death in the US by different drugs since 1999, showing a horrifying trend. Data: ourwoldindata. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El gráfico de tarta</title>
      <link>/es/2018/el-gr%C3%A1fico-de-tarta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2018 11:23:32 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/2018/el-gr%C3%A1fico-de-tarta/</guid>
      <description>Bienvenido a mi blog! Soy Dominic Royé, investigador y docente de geografía física en la Universidad de Santiago de Compostela. Una de mis pasiones es la programación en R para visualizar y analizar cualquier tipo de datos. Por eso, mi idea de iniciar este blog tiene su origen en las publicaciones que he ido haciendo en el útimo año en Twitter sobre diferentes temas visualizando datos que describen el mundo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>