<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphs on Dominic Royé</title>
    <link>/en/graphs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graphs on Dominic Royé</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2020 Dominic Royé. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/graphs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate and Weather</title>
      <link>/en/graphs/climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/graphs/climate/</guid>
      <description>Probability of a summer day (maximum temperature greater than 25ºC) through the year in Australia. Data: SILO.
   Probability of a frost day (minimum temperature less than 0ºC) through the year in Europe. Data: E-OBS 18e.
   Probability of a frost day (minimum temperature less than 0ºC/32ºF) through the year in the Contiguous United States. Data: PRISM. Platform: Google Earth Engine.
Concentration of daily precipitation in the contiguous United States 1981-2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Environment</title>
      <link>/en/graphs/environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/graphs/environment/</guid>
      <description>Light pollution by municipality in 2015. What is the municipality that emits the most artificial light? The map shows the Coefficient of Variation (standard deviation/mean) of each municipalities. Data: VIIRS Nighttime Lights NOAA (2015).Which coast has more light pollution in Peninsular Spain? The coast margins include a buffer of 5km. Data: VIIRS Nighttime Lights NOAA (2016).Light pollution by municipality in 2015. What is the municipality that emits the most artificial light?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geography</title>
      <link>/en/graphs/geography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/graphs/geography/</guid>
      <description>Spatial patterns of cemeteries in Northwest Spain (number per 1,000 inhabitants) based on OpenStreetMaps. Data: OpenStreetMap, IGE More: post.Spatial patterns of cemeteries in Spain (number per 10,000 inhabitants) based on OpenStreetMaps. Data: OpenStreetMap, INE More: post.Urban growth seen by the year of construction for the six largest Spanish cities.. Data: Catastro.Animation of urban growth seen by the year of construction in Valencia, Spain.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>