<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>temperature on Dominic Royé</title>
    <link>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/tags/temperature/</link>
    <description>Recent content in temperature on Dominic Royé</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2020 Dominic Royé. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dominicroye.github.io/en/tags/temperature/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A heatmap as calendar</title>
      <link>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/a-heatmap-as-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/a-heatmap-as-calendar/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was looking for a visual representation to show the daily changes of temperature, precipitation and wind in an application xeo81.shinyapps.io/MeteoExtremosGalicia (in Spanish), which led me to use a heatmap in the form of a calendar. The shiny application is updated every four hours with new data showing calendars for each weather station. The heatmap as a calendar allows you to visualize any variable with a daily time reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate animation of maximum temperatures</title>
      <link>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/climate-animation-of-maximum-temperatures/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/climate-animation-of-maximum-temperatures/</guid>
      <description>In the field of data visualization, the animation of spatial data in its temporal dimension can show fascinating changes and patterns. As a result of one of the last publications in the social networks that I have made, I was asked to make a post about how I created it. Well, here we go to start with an example of data from mainland Spain. You can find more animations in the graphics section of my blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualize climate anomalies</title>
      <link>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/visualize-climate-anomalies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/visualize-climate-anomalies/</guid>
      <description>When we visualize precipitation and temperature anomalies, we simply use time series as bar graph indicating negative and positive values in red and blue. However, in order to have a better overview we need both anomalies in a single graph. In this way we could more easly answer the question of whether a particular season or month was dry-warm or wet-cold, and even compare these anomalies in the context of previous years.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>