<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>climate on Dominic Royé</title>
    <link>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/tags/climate/</link>
    <description>Recent content in climate on Dominic Royé</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2021 Dominic Royé. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://dominicroye.github.io/en/tags/climate/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A heatmap as calendar</title>
      <link>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/a-heatmap-as-calendar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/a-heatmap-as-calendar/</guid>
      <description>Recently I was looking for a visual representation to show the daily changes of temperature, precipitation and wind in an application xeo81.shinyapps.io/MeteoExtremosGalicia (in Spanish), which led me to use a heatmap in the form of a calendar. The shiny application is updated every four hours with new data showing calendars for each weather station. The heatmap as a calendar allows you to visualize any variable with a daily time reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visualize climate anomalies</title>
      <link>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/visualize-climate-anomalies/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/2020/visualize-climate-anomalies/</guid>
      <description>When we visualize precipitation and temperature anomalies, we simply use time series as bar graph indicating negative and positive values in red and blue. However, in order to have a better overview we need both anomalies in a single graph. In this way we could more easly answer the question of whether a particular season or month was dry-warm or wet-cold, and even compare these anomalies in the context of previous years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Climate and Weather</title>
      <link>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/graphs/climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dominicroye.github.io/en/graphs/climate/</guid>
      <description>Videos 
   Smoothed daily rainfall throughout the year in Australia. Data: SILO.
   Smoothed daily maximum temperature throughout the year in Australia. Data: SILO.
   How do the spatial patterns of daily precipitation change throughout the year in Europe? Data: E-OBS.
   Smoothed daily maximum temperature throughout the year in the contiguous USA. Data: PRISM.
   Smoothed daily maximum temperature throughout the year in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>