<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphs on Dominic Royé</title>
    <link>/es/graphs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graphs on Dominic Royé</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2019 Dominic Royé. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/es/graphs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clima y tiempo</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/climate/</guid>
      <description>Probability of a frost day (minimum temperature less than 0ºC) through the year in Europe. Data: E-OBS 18e.
   Probability of a frost day (minimum temperature less than 0ºC/32ºF) through the year in the Contiguous United States. Data: PRISM. Platform: Google Earth Engine.
62 years of annual anomalies of precipitation (%) in peninsular Spain in a single graphic. Data: SPREAD.Summer anomaly of temperature and precipitation in Barcelona 1914-2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geografía</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/geography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/geography/</guid>
      <description>Urban growth of Santiag de Compostela from before 1800 until today. Data: Catastro INSPIRE QGIS-Plugin.Flight routes of the ten busiest airports by passenger traffic in Europe based on 24 hour data for each airport. Data: https://www.flightradar24.com/. More: article (spanish)The Sky View Factor is very useful urban spatial indicator for radiation and thermal environmental assessment. SVF describes how visible is the sky (0: the entire sky is blocked from view; 1: free view on the whole sky).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medio ambiente</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/environment/</guid>
      <description>Light pollution by municipality in 2015. What is the municipality that emits the most artificial light? The map shows the Coefficient of Variation (standard deviation/mean) of each municipalities. Data: VIIRS Nighttime Lights NOAA (2015).Which coast has more light pollution in Peninsular Spain? The coast margins include a buffer of 5km. Data: VIIRS Nighttime Lights NOAA (2016).Light pollution by municipality in 2015. What is the municipality that emits the most artificial light?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Populación</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/population/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/population/</guid>
      <description>Population pyramid of Galicia since 1975. Data: IGEPopulation pyramid of Galician provinces since 1975. Data: IGEPopulation pyramid of Spanish autonomous community since 1998. Data: INEMigration flows between Spanish autonomous communities in 2008. Data: INE </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salud</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/health/</guid>
      <description>Evolution of adult obesity in Europe between 1975 and 2016. Data: ourwoldindata, script.National Overdose Death in the US by different drugs since 1999, showing a horrifying trend. Data: ourwoldindata. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>