<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphs on Dominic Royé</title>
    <link>/es/graphs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graphs on Dominic Royé</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2019 Dominic Royé. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/es/graphs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clima y tiempo</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/climate/</guid>
      <description>Probability of a frost day (minimum temperature less than 0ºC) through the year in Europe. Data: E-OBS 18e.
   Probability of a frost day (minimum temperature less than 0ºC/32ºF) through the year in the Contiguous United States. Data: PRISM. Platform: Google Earth Engine.
Índice de Concentración de la precipitación diaria en EEUU. Datos: PRISM. Más detalles aquí.Promedio de Grados Día de Calefacción y Refrigeración (1950-2018) en España.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geografía</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/geography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/geography/</guid>
      <description>Indice de Precios al Consumidor: Alquiler de viviendas (variación anual) 2002-2019 en España por provincia. Datos: INE.Tiempo de viaje a centros urbanos de alta densidad a través del transporte de superficie en España. Datos: resourcewatch.org.Ranking del tiempo de viaje a centros urbanos de alta densidad a través del transporte de superficie según provincias españolas. Datos: resourcewatch.org.Inspirado por el gran trabajo de @geo_coe, he creado un mapa de elevación para el río serpenteante Ebro, tramo medio entre Logroño y Zaragoza en España.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medio ambiente</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/environment/</guid>
      <description>Light pollution by municipality in 2015. What is the municipality that emits the most artificial light? The map shows the Coefficient of Variation (standard deviation/mean) of each municipalities. Data: VIIRS Nighttime Lights NOAA (2015).Which coast has more light pollution in Peninsular Spain? The coast margins include a buffer of 5km. Data: VIIRS Nighttime Lights NOAA (2016).Light pollution by municipality in 2015. What is the municipality that emits the most artificial light?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Populación</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/population/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/population/</guid>
      <description>Population point clouds of Ourense since 1975. Data: IGEPopulation pyramid of Galicia since 1975. Data: IGEPopulation pyramid of Galician provinces since 1975. Data: IGEPopulation pyramid of Spanish autonomous community since 1998. Data: INEMigration flows between Spanish autonomous communities in 2008. Data: INE </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salud</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/health/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/health/</guid>
      <description>Evolution of adult obesity in Europe between 1975 and 2016. Data: ourwoldindata, script.National Overdose Death in the US by different drugs since 1999, showing a horrifying trend. Data: ourwoldindata. </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>