<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Graphs on Dominic Royé</title>
    <link>/es/graphs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Graphs on Dominic Royé</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2020 Dominic Royé. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/es/graphs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Clima y tiempo</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/climate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/climate/</guid>
      <description>Videos 
   Smoothed daily rainfall throughout the year in Australia. Data: SILO.
   Smoothed daily maximum temperature throughout the year in Australia. Data: SILO.
   How do the spatial patterns of daily precipitation change throughout the year in Europe? Data: E-OBS.
   Smoothed daily maximum temperature throughout the year in the contiguous USA. Data: PRISM.
   Smoothed daily maximum temperature throughout the year in Europe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Geografía</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/geography/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/geography/</guid>
      <description>Videos 
   3d model of Nazaré Canyon off the coast of #Nazare, Portugal. Well known as hotspot for big wave surfing.

Gráficos 
Las venas azules de la Tierra para la Península Ibérica. La ciencia es arte. El ancho de la línea refleja el tamaño del río. Datos: https://hydrosheds.org/River flow directions were estimated using vectorial data.River flow directions were estimated using vectorial data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medio ambiente</title>
      <link>/es/graphs/environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/es/graphs/environment/</guid>
      <description>Daily contribution of coal to electricity generation in Germany. Data: energy-charts.deLa contribución diaria del carbón a la generación eléctrica en España desde 2011. Hasta el 17 de agosto de 2019 no ha habido ningún día con menos del 1%. Data: REDataLight pollution by municipality in 2015. What is the municipality that emits the most artificial light? The map shows the Coefficient of Variation (standard deviation/mean) of each municipalities.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>